Privacy Policy
==============

#### 

Last Modified: November 25, 2024

I. Introduction
---------------

The following Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes how BN Media, LLC (“Bibleminute,” “BN Media,” “we,” “us,” “Operator”) collects, uses, and shares personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected (collectively referred to as “Data”) through website, mobile website, mobile applications, and social media platforms we operate (collectively, the “Products”) and the services, features, advertisements or content we offer, including your communications with us or others through our messaging and phone services (collectively with the Products, the “Services”). The Policy applies when you use any of these Products or Services regardless of how you access or use the Services. This Policy describes the kinds of Data we may gather when you use the Products or Services, how we may use your Data, when we might disclose your Data, and how you can manage your Data.

II. Revisions
-------------

We may change the Policy at any time by posting revisions to the Policy on the Products or Services. If we make material changes to how we treat your Data, we will notify you through general notice through the Products. If you do not accept all of the terms, conditions and notices set forth in the Policy, you must not use the Products or Services. Please note that our Products and Services are under constant development. This Policy may therefore be modified and updated at any time and on an ongoing basis. Each such modification will be effective upon posting on the Products and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of such revised Privacy Policy. The date the Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. Your continued use of the Products or Services after Operator posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review the Privacy Policy periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices.

III. Collection of Information from Children
--------------------------------------------

The Products and Services are not directed to, or intended for use by, anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you only may use the Products and Services with permission from your parents or legal guardians. Operator does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, do not use or provide any information on any of the Operator’s Products or Services (websites, apps, etc.) or through any of its features, register on any of the Operator’s Products or Services (websites, apps, etc.), make any purchases through any of the Operator’s Products or Services (websites, apps, etc.) use any of the interactive or public comment features of the Operator’s Products or Services (websites, apps, etc.) or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If a child under 18 submits information through any part of the Products or Services, and we become aware that the person submitting the information is under 18, we will delete this information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at [Do Not Sell My Data](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3)

IV. Information Collected
-------------------------

Type of Information Collected. When you use the Products or Services, we may collect several types of information about you and/or your use of the Products or Services. The general categories of information include Personally Identifiable Information or “PII” as well as non-personally identifiable information (“non-PII”).

PII includes, but is not limited to, the following:

* Information you provide to us. We collect your personal data or information when you use our Services. There are numerous circumstances where you may volunteer, be required or invited to provide us with personal information, such as when you create an account, enter a contest, subscribe to our publications, newsletters, and other content, register for or use our Products or Services, submit content or post a comment, send us an e-mail or request information, or send messages through our Message Center (including e-mail, text or other messages). This information may include:
    * Your name, any alias, e-mail address, birth date, gender, street address, and telephone number(s);
    * Employment information or other demographic information including but not limited to employment history and educational background;
    * Audio, digital, video, or other electronic information provided by you, including, but not limited to, audio and/or video recordings;
    * Social security numbers;
    * Driver’s license; and
    * You may also provide us with your bank account number, credit card number, debit card number or any other financial information provided by you.

* Account information. We may assign you a user id, account name, unique personal or online identifier, other identifiers that permit physical or online contact with you, or any information about you collected online and maintained in personally identifiable form in combination with any of the preceding categories.

* Usage Information. We may collect certain usage information associated with you. This may include:
    * Internet or other similar network activity on the Operator’s web sites, including browsing history, search history or information regarding your interaction with the Products or Services, your advertising preferences, and your communications with us or through us, the user segment or category into which you as a user are classified by us internally;
    * Data about the pages you visit, the access time, frequency and duration of visits, the links on which you click and other actions you take as part of your use of our Products and Services;
    * Geolocation data;
    * Data that is generated as part of your transactions (purchases, listings, messages, ads, viewings) using the Products and Services;
    * Data that is generated through your communications through use of the Products and Services, including your communications with us, our third-party providers, or other users of the Services (including, but not limited all messages and data generated through the Message Center); and
    * Data about your activities and interactions with our advertising partners including data about the advertisements you were shown, how often they were shown, when and where they were shown, and whether you took any action, such as clicking on an advertisement or making a purchase.

* Information from Third Parties. We may receive information about you from third parties consistent with relevant law and combine it with information we receive from or about you, including, information from social media websites or information from publicly or commercially available sources. This information could include:
    * When you engage with the Products or Services and their content through such third-party sites, plug-ins or applications, we may have access to certain information from your social media profile, such as your name, photo, gender, birthday, location, videos, your list of friends, etc.
    * When you link your account to any other account on third-party web site, including but not limited to a social media web site, we may have access to data regarding your use of that web site as well as personal data such third party web sites may have collected about you.
    * Commercial information, including records of purchasing habits;
    * Engagement with our Products and Services through third-party social networking sites or social media plug-ins and applications; and
    * Information from other public sources including, but not limited to, data from credit agencies or bureaus or data from data aggregators.

Non-PII includes information about your use of the Products and Services. We may collect information about your use of the Products and Services including:

* Device information. We may collect your computer or mobile device model, IP address, operating system version, browser type, language and settings, device type and settings, and other unique device identifiers.
* Location information. We may collect your location when using the Products and services on our website and apps. We may collect and store your device's source IP address and/or latitude and longitude, which may disclose your device's approximate or precise location when you access the Products or Services. Advertisements and certain content, including from third parties, may be directed to you based on this data.
* Usage information. We may collect information about the Products or Services you use, the time, duration, and date of your use of the Services, your interaction with content offered through the Products and Services, how you contacted the Products or Services, search terms used, and browsing history. We also collect information stored using cookies, mobile ad identifiers, and similar technologies set on your device. Our servers may automatically keep an activity log of your use of the Products or Services.
* Inferential Data. We may use your personal information or other information we collect from you or your activity on the Operator’s web sites to create consumer profiles reflecting preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities or aptitudes.

Certain features available within the Products or Services will require you to submit PII about yourself as a condition of participation. Some of the features may be offered by us, while others may be offered by third parties. (For example, you may be required to submit PII in order to enter a contest we conduct, to order certain products and services we offer, or to receive news updates by email from a third-party news source.) When you choose to submit PII to a third party in connection with your use of the Products or Services, the third party’s privacy policy, rather than this Policy, will control the use of your PII. YOU CAN ALWAYS REFUSE TO PROVIDE PII TO US, BUT THIS MAY RESULT IN DECREASED FUNCTIONALITY OF ANY OF THE OPERATOR’S WEB SITES FOR YOU AND LIMIT YOUR ABILITY TO RECEIVE INFORMATION ABOUT PRODUCTS OR SERVICES THAT MAY BE OF PARTICULAR INTEREST TO YOU.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Operator’s web sites, or transmitted to other users of the Operator’s web sites, or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users of the Operator’s web sites with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

V. How Information is Collected
-------------------------------

We collect information both actively and passively. For example, we will collect information about you that you voluntarily provide while using the Products and Services. In addition to information provided directly by you, we (and third parties that offer features through the Products or Services) may collect non-PII through the use of “cookies,” “web beacons,” or by other electronic means

**Information We Collect Automatically.** If you use the Products or Services, read or download information from the Products or Services, your web or mobile browser may automatically send us your internet or other network activity.

**Information You Give To Us and Information We Collect From Others.** If you use the Products or Services, or you otherwise use or purchase our Products or Services, we receive and store information you enter on the Products or Services, or that you give us in-person, via telephone, email, or otherwise. We may also collect personal information from third parties that operate (a) portions of the Products or Services on our behalf or (b) independent websites. When we obtain personal data from third parties, we will treat the acquired information like the information that we collect ourselves.

VI. Cookie Policy: How We Collect Information  
From You and From Other Third Parties
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Generally**. We may place, or allow to be placed, cookies, web beacons and similar technologies on our Products and Services to store your username for easy logon, store your preferences, keep you logged in, perform analytics, analyze traffic, personalize content, and offer advertisements that match your interest. We may use these technologies to collect information when you use our Products and Services such as your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, browsing and conversion information in order to provide you with a customized user experience. These technologies may include Google Analytics and similar providers. You can learn more about how Google uses the information collected through this service at: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.bibleminute.co/www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

* Cookies. In general, a cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive, where it can be used to identify your computer. Cookies can be used to measure website usage, improve navigation around website, and personalize a returning visitor’s experience on the website. In most cases, you can set your browser to turn off cookies or to notify you before you receive one so that you can decide whether to accept it or not. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of the features on the Site, we recommend that you leave them turned on. If you block or reject our cookies, some of the features on the Products may not work for you. You can refer to the instructions for your browser to learn more about these functions.
* Web Beacons. We, our third-party service providers, advertisers and partners also may use “web beacons” or similar technologies. Web beacons are small strings of code placed on a web page to collect data about how visitors use the Products or Services. For example, web beacons may be used to count the number of users who visit the Products or Services, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor to the Products or Services. If you set your browser to turn off cookies, web beacons and similar technologies will detect your visits to the Products or Services, but they will not associate your activity on the Products or Services with information that otherwise would be stored in cookies.

**Advertisements (Including Direct, Targeted, Third Party).** In order to continue to bring you the Products and Services, we use advertising in our Products and Services. Some of these advertisements may contain cookies, collect information, such as your IP address and device type. We may also display targeted advertisements to you based on information you have supplied to us. For instance, if you have expressed an interest in a particular product, we may supply you with advertisements from selected marketing partners of that product. They will not, however, receive your personal information unless you volunteer it to such advertisers.

We also work with ad network partners that display ads on our Products. To improve your ad experience on the Products and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to our ad network partners based on your browser’s activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see on the Product or other Internet websites, apps, etc., is relevant to you. [Click here](https://support.google.com/admanager/answer/2839090?hl=en&&ref_topic=7395141) and [here](https://myadcenter.google.com/home?sasb=true) to learn more about our ad partner’s ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you.

We also may allow our affiliates and third-party advertising companies (including ad servers, ad agencies, technology vendors, or providers of sponsored content) (collectively “Third Parties”) to use cookies on our Products and Services. These Third Parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Operator’s web sites. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content on our Products as well as other websites, apps, platforms, etc. you visit. Some of these parties may use cookies in ways that we do not. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access all or certain parts of the Products and Services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log onto our Sites.

Please note, we do not control tracking technologies used by Third Parties on any of the Operator’s web sites or how they may be used. Third Parties have the ability to set and access their cookies on your computer. Third Parties’ use of their own cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. For more information about these specialized cookies and other technologies, and to learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt out of this type of advertising for some companies, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [http://networkadvertising.org/optout\_nonppii.asp](http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). When using a mobile application, you may receive tailored in-application advertisements. Each operating system provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the instructions and/or the privacy settings for your operating system to find out how to opt out of tailored in-application advertisements.

If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**Third-Party Websites.** The Products allow advertising by Third Parties that provide links to a Third-Party website. These Third Parties may use the technology described above to send (or “serve”) directly to your browser the advertisements that appear on our Products. When this happens, Third Parties automatically receive PII, such as your IP address, as well as non-PII and other information from your computer and browser, including your cookie information. They also may use cookies, Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies to deliver advertisements; collect information about the effectiveness of their advertisements; collect anonymous information about your visits to the Products, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad; or customize the advertising content you see. Third Parties will not collect your name, address, or other PII, unless you affirmatively provide it to them. Third Parties have the ability to set and access their cookies on your computer. Third Parties’ use of their own cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. For more information about these specialized cookies and other technologies, and to learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt out of this type of advertising for some companies, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [http://networkadvertising.org/optout\_nonppii.asp](http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). When using a mobile application, you may receive tailored in-application advertisements. Each operating system provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the instructions and/or the privacy settings for your operating system to find out how to opt out of tailored in-application advertisements.

Please note, clicking on an advertisement, links or other elements on the Products may take you to an entirely different site. Links to other sites may use our Product logos or styles as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may use their own cookies and may collect data and make use of that data in ways that the Products would not. After you leave our Products, this Policy will no longer apply to PII or any other data collected from or provided by you. You should check the other web site’s applicable privacy policy to determine how it will handle such data.

**Social Media.** We or Our third-party service providers, advertisers, and partners may use technologies like cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, device or other identifiers and local storage to identify parts of the Products and Services you have visited and/or purchased, identify advertisements you have seen, and otherwise deliver, secure, and understand products, services and ads, on and off Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn, YouTube, and other social media platforms. These technologies also may be used to gather information for remarketing to similar audiences on our Products. Third party advertisements displayed on the Products may also contain cookies set by third party advertisers. The Operator does not control these cookies and is not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site; users of the Products and Services should check the privacy policy of the third-party advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.

The third parties with whom the following categories of personal information are shared for a business purpose may include, but are not limited to, those corresponding third parties listed below:

| **Categories of Personal Information** | **Third Parties Disclosed to:** |
| --- | --- |
| Category A: Personal Information and Identifiers | Affiliates, Service Providers, third-party advertisers, and analytics providers |
| --- | --- |
| Category B: Protected Class Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |
| Category C: Commercial Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |
| Category D: Biometric Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |
| Category E: Internet and Network Information | Affiliates, Service Providers, third parties, such as third-party advertisers and analytics providers |
| --- | --- |
| Category F: Geolocation Information | Affiliates, Service Providers, third parties, such as third-party advertisers, and advertising and list brokering networks and analytics providers |
| --- | --- |
| Category G: Sensory Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |
| Category H: Employment Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |
| Category I: Non-Public Education Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |
| Category J: Profile Information | Service Providers, Affiliates, Partners, Parent or Subsidiary organizations, internet cookie data recipients, data brokers or aggregators, social networks, operating systems and platforms, government entities, data analytic providers, internet service providers, advertising networks. |
| --- | --- |

VII. Video Services
-------------------

Your video content viewing and associated media consumption activities (collectively “Viewing Activities”) may be collected when you use the Services. By watching video content on or through the Services, you are consenting to share your personal information, together with your Viewing Activities, with third parties acting on our behalf and with our advertising and analytic partners described in this Notice in the ordinary course of business.

VIII. How Information Is Used and Shared
----------------------------------------

We may use information we collect to do the following, among other things:

* To present the Operator’s websites and its contents to you;
* To offer the Products and Services;
* To monitor and analyze web traffic and online behavior for search engine optimization and social media marketing;
* To manage security, including monitoring individuals with access to the Products and Services, applications, systems, or facilities, investigation of threats, and as needed, for any data security breach notification;
* To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or from other users of the Operator’s web sites;
* To fulfill any other purposes for which you provide us information;
* To allow you to interact with the messaging and social networking functionalities as well as to participate in other interactive features associated with the Operator’s web sites;
* To notify you about changes to the Operator’s web sites or any products or services we offer or provide through it;
* To contact you;
* To respond to your inquiries;
* To provide notices with respect to your account;
* To troubleshoot or provide you with technical support;
* To create and to manage your account;
* To place calls or send text messages through automated means that include prerecorded messages that include advertising or non-advertising messages;
* To place calls or send text messages manually that include advertising or advertising-related information;
* To send you communications you have requested, including e-mails, newsletters and other electronic communications;
* To enroll you in contests, programs or other offers you request;
* To inform you about other products and services that may be of interest to you;
* To deliver advertising;
* To process payment for purchases you have made;
* To protect against or identify possible fraud;
* To manage and mitigate risk;
* View and incorporate content hosted on external sites;
* To resolve a dispute;
* To conduct a poll or survey;
* To analyze the use of our Products and Services;
* To personalize the content of our Products and Services;
* To develop new products and services;
* To improve our Products, Services and overall business;
* To understand how you arrived at the Products or Services;
* To manage the Products and Services;
* To enforce our Terms of Use and any other user agreements incorporated by reference;
* To enforce the terms of this Policy;
* To enforce our legal rights;
* To comply with the law;
* For other uses we may disclose to you at the point of collection, as authorized by you, or as otherwise permitted by law, and
* For any other purposes with your consent.

IX. Disclosure
--------------

WE MAY DISCLOSE PII ABOUT YOU TO A THIRD PARTY FOR COMPENSATION.  
IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE UTAH NOTICE OF INTENT TO SELL NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ACT, WE MAY CHOOSE TO DISCLOSE NON-PUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, THE CONSUMER, TO A THIRD PARTY FOR COMPENSATION.

In addition, we may disclose PII and Non-PII as follows:

* For all reasons set forth above in “How Information is Used and Shared”.
* We may share your telephone number(s) with our authorized services providers that may use automated or manual dialing means to contact you to carry out any of the activities identified in “How Information is Used and Shared”.
* To service providers or parties that we have engaged to perform business-related functions on our behalf. This may include service providers that conduct research and analytics, create content, provide customer, technical or operational support, conduct or support marketing, fulfill orders and user requests, administer contests, maintain databases, send or support online or mobile advertising and otherwise support our Products and Services.
* To our business partners or joint marketing partners.
* To our advertising and marketing partners.
* To other third parties that support our Products and Services including, but not limited to, third parties that may provide financing.
* In response to legal processes such as court orders or subpoenas, law enforcement or government agency requests or similar requests or otherwise if we determine that disclosure is prudent to comply with law, to assist in the identification, investigation or prosecution of fraud, or to comply with requests of law enforcement or data protection agencies.
* To the extent that you submitted your e-mail address and/or phone number to a particular buyer or seller through the Products and Services, you agree and expressly consent to be contacted by the other party by various means, including by phone, text message, email, automatic telephone dial system and/or an artificial or prerecorded voice.
* With affiliates of Operator so they can provide, improve and communicate with you about their own, or their marketing partners’ products and services.
* In the event that Operator is considering a sale of its business, in its entirety or a component thereof, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or a portion thereof, or a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Operator’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, Data, including PII, may be one of the transferred assets, and may therefore be used by a third-party acquirer in accordance with this Policy. Such use by a third party may include review of PII, using such PII to contact you either before or after such a transfer or sale, use or transfer of non-PII before or after such a transfer or sale, or for other purposes.

In addition, we may share your information as described below:

* Information You Elect to Share: You may choose to share information with Third Parties by clicking on links to Third Parties from within the Products or Services. In addition, you may elect to share information, including PII, through the Product or Services by, for instance, posting comments on comment boards or listing classified advertisements. Some of your activity on the Products or Services, including content you have posted, is public by default. Some of this content may include PII.
* Third-Party Advertisers and Websites: We may share your PII and non-PII with Third Parties as described in the section above titled Third-Party Advertising and Third-Party Websites.
* Information Disclosed to Vendors, Partners, Service Providers, and Others for Business Purposes: We contract with vendors to provide services related to the Products and Services and may share information with such vendors in order to provide products or services to you or to help maintain the Products and Services. We also may share PII and non-PII with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business.
* Information Disclosed for the Protection of the Products and Services and for Others. We may disclose PII and Non-PII when (1) required by law or to respond to legal process or lawful requests, including from law enforcement; (2) when we believe it is necessary to prevent, investigate, or address (a) possible illegal activities, including fraud, (b) violation of our Terms of Use, (c) violation of this Policy, or (d) threats to the physical safety of any person; or (3) to protect our rights or property.

X. Forums
---------

The Products and Services may include forums (such as message boards, chat rooms, comment boards, and reviews) that enable users to post a comment or communicate with each other. The Operator is under no obligation to moderate or edit the forums and will not be responsible for the content or use of any material posted on any forum within the Products or Services. The Operator retains the right to delete at any time and for any reason any material posted within the Products or Services.

XI. Information Security
------------------------

**How Do We Protect Personal Data?** We take information security seriously, and we use reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect the PII we collect from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Operator protects data using administrative, technical, and physical safeguards. When we use third-party service providers, we ask those providers to implement similar safeguards. However, we cannot guarantee that your information is completely secure either within the Company or on the systems of third-party service providers.

But we have no control over the security of other websites on the Internet that you might visit even when a link may appear to those websites on our Products or through our Services. If you share your computer or use a computer that is accessed by the general public, remember to sign off and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This will help to ensure that others cannot access your PII.

Additionally, and as you are likely aware, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take commercially reasonable steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your PII, searches or other communications will always remain secure. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to the Operator’s web sites. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on any of the Operator’s web sites.

In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your PII, we will notify you if reasonably possible and as reasonably necessary so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may notify you under such circumstances using the e-mail address(es) we have on record for you. You should also take care with how you handle and disclose your PII. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at [http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/) for information about how to protect against identity theft.

#### How Long Do We Keep Your Personal Data?

We retain personal data we collect from you when we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (i.e., to provide you with the Services you have requested or to comply with applicable legal requirements). When we no longer have an ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will physically destroy, delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your personal data and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

XII. General Contact Information
--------------------------------

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or exercising any of your privacy rights, please contact us at the telephone number, email address or mailing address listed below:

Telephone Number: 1-833-796-0136 (PIN: 141439)  
Email Address: [copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com](mailto:copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com)

XIII. Your State Privacy Rights
-------------------------------

If you are a California, Nevada or Virginia resident, your state’s laws may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. Please see the state-specific sections below:

### Important Information for California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our Product and Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at [Do Not Sell My Data](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3).

These additional disclosures for California residents apply only to individuals who reside in California. The California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended and together with all applicable regulations (“CCPA”) provides additional rights to know, delete and opt out, and requires businesses collecting or disclosing personal information to provide notices and means to exercise those rights. The words used in this section have the meanings given to them in the CCPA, which may be broader than their common meaning. For example, the definition of “personal information” under the CCPA includes your name, but also more general information such as age.

#### Notice of Collection

The categories of personal information that we may have collected – as described by the CCPA – in the past 12 months are:

Identifiers: name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol (IP) address, email address, account name. We may use this data to provide customers with an account, enabling them to post listings or messages, or subscribe to our newsletters. Additionally, we use online identifiers to understand how consumers use our products and services.

Customer records information: name, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit, or debit card number. We collect this information when a user performs a payment transaction on one of our services.

Commercial information: We use a unique identifier to track consumer behavior on our products. We then use that data to personalize content and or advertising products to the consumer.

Internet or other electronic network activity information: We collect this data specific to our websites and applications. We do not operate a web browser or search technology, but we track searches performed on our website. We do this for a few purposes. We allow users to create saved searches and alerts. Saved searches and alerts enable users to opt-in to a notification service. When the user creates a saved search, if a new product is posted on our service that matches their search criteria, we will send them an email or mobile phone alert. We also use their search behavior to personalize content and advertising.

Geolocation data: When using our service, a user can search for information using location data such as a city or zip code. Furthermore, on a mobile device, users can opt-in to the mobile device geolocation service to show the user listings from a selected mile radius from their current geolocation.

Inferences: We use consumer behavior to create profiles and make inferences about future consumer behavior.

We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes and sharing practices described in our policy above.

We do not generally “sell” personal information as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. However, to the extent “sale” under the CCPA is interpreted to include advertising technology activities such as those disclosed in the above sections as a “sale,” we provide you the option to request that we not “sell” your personal information. We do not sell the personal information of minors known to be under the age of 16 without affirmative authorization.

We sell or disclose the following categories of personal information for commercial purposes: identifiers, demographic information, commercial information, internet activity, geolocation data and inferences. We use and partner with different types of entities to assist with our daily operations and manage our services.

#### Right to Know and Delete

If you are a California resident, you have the right to delete the personal information we have collected from you and the right to know certain information about our data practices in the preceding 12 months (also called a data portability request). In particular, you have the right to request the following from us:

* The categories of personal information we have collected about you;
* The categories of sources from which the personal information was collected;
* The categories of personal information about you we disclosed for a business purpose or sold;
* The categories of third parties to whom the personal information was disclosed for a business purpose or sold;
* If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing: if sold, personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased, and if disclosed for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained;
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the personal information; and
* The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.

To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request [here](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3). You may also contact us by calling 1-833-796-0136 and entering 141439 as the PIN You may also contact us by email at [copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com](mailto:copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com). We will use the information you provide to us solely for the purpose of verifying your request and locating your data, if any, within our records. Please note, under California law, such requests can be made a maximum of twice per twelve-month period.

We have a duty as the holder of certain personal information to verify your identity when making requests to know or delete personal information and to ensure that dissemination of that information would not cause harm to you if it were distributed to another person. To verify your identity, we will request and collect additional personal information from you to match it against our records. We may ask for additional information or documentation if we feel it is necessary to confirm your identity with the necessary degree of certainty. We may communicate with you through email, a secure message center, or other reasonably necessary and appropriate means. We do have the right to deny requests under certain circumstances. In such cases, we will notify you of the reasons for denial. We will not provide you with specific pieces of personal information if the disclosure creates a substantial, articulable, and unreasonable risk to the security of that personal information, your account with us, or the security of our systems or networks. In no event will we disclose, if we have collected it, your Social Security number, driver’s license number or other government-issued identification number, financial account number, any health insurance or medical identification number, an account password, or security questions and answers.

#### Right to Opt-Out

To the extent we sell your personal information as the term “sell” is defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information by us to third parties at any time. You may submit a request to opt-out of by clicking [Do Not Sell My Data](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3). You may also contact us by calling 1-833-796-0136 and entering 141439 as the PIN You may also contact us by email at [copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com](mailto:copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com).

#### Non-discrimination

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for exercising any of your rights.

#### Authorized Agent

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request via an authorized agent acting on your behalf. To do so, we must receive written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.

#### California Do Not Track Disclosure

Certain web browsers may allow you to enable a “do not track” option that sends signals to the websites you visit indicating that you do not want your online activities tracked. This is different than blocking cookies as browsers with the “do not track” option selected may still accept cookies. Right now, there is no industry standard for how companies should respond to “do not track” signals, although one may be adopted in the future. We do not respond to “do not track” signals at this time. If we do so in the future, we will modify this Policy accordingly. More information about “do not track” is available at [www.allaboutdnt.com](https://www.bibleminute.co/www.allaboutdnt.com).

### Important Information for Colorado Residents: Your Colorado Privacy Rights

These additional disclosures for Colorado residents apply only to individuals who reside in Colorado. The Colorado Privacy Act provides additional rights to confirm and access, correct, delete, obtain a copy, and opt-out, and requires businesses collecting or disclosing personal information to provide notices and means to exercise those rights. The words used in this section have the meanings given to them in the CPA, which may be broader than their common meaning.

#### Notice of Collection

The categories of personal information that we may have collected in the past 12 months are:

Identifiers: name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol (IP) address, email address, account name. We may use this data to provide customers with an account which enables them to post listings or messages, or to subscribe to our newsletters. Additionally, we use online identifiers to understand how consumers use our products and services.

Customer records information: name, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit, or debit card number. We collect this information when a user performs a payment transaction on one of our services.

Commercial information: We use a unique identifier to track consumer behavior on our products. We then use that data to personalize content and/or advertising products to the consumer.

Internet or other electronic network activity information: We collect this data specific to our websites and applications. We do not operate a web browser or search technology, but we may track searches performed on our website. We do this for a few purposes. We allow users to create saved searches and alerts. Saved searches and alerts enable users to opt-in to a notification service. When the user creates a saved search, if a new product is posted on our service that matches their search criteria, we will send them an email or mobile phone alert. We also use their search behavior to personalize content and advertising.

Geolocation data: When using our service, a user can search for information using location data such as a city or zip code. Furthermore, on a mobile device, users can opt-in to the mobile device geolocation service to show the user listings from a selected mile radius from their current geolocation.

Inferences: We use consumer behavior to create profiles and make inferences about future consumer behavior.

We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes and sharing practices described in our policy above.

We do not generally “sell” personal information as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. However, to the extent “sale” under the CPA is interpreted to include advertising technology activities such as those disclosed in the above sections as a “sale,” we provide you the option to request that we not “sell” your personal information. We do not sell the personal information of minors known to be under the age of 16 without affirmative authorization.

We may sell or disclose the following categories of personal information for commercial purposes: identifiers, demographic information, commercial information, internet activity, geolocation data and inferences. We use and partner with different types of entities to assist with our daily operations and manage our services.

**What Are My Rights Under the CPA?** If you are a Colorado resident and are engaged in a direct business relationship with Company as a consumer for the provision of the Sites or Services, you may have the following rights:

* Right to Know and to Access. You may confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data. You may also request access to your personal data.

Though you may request specific pieces of your personal information that we have collected, we may not provide the following information in order to protect the security of such information: social security numbers, driver’s license or other state or government-issued identification numbers, bank account numbers or other financial information, any health insurance or medical identification numbers or related information, account passwords or security questions and answers.

* Right to Correct. You may request the correction of any inaccuracies in your personal data, taking into account the nature of the personal data and the purposes of the processing of the personal data.
* Right to Delete. Under certain, limited circumstances, you may request that we delete personal information that we have collected from you or from a third party. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity, we will review your request to see if an exception allowing us to retain the information applies.
* Right to Obtain a Copy. You may request a copy of your personal data, which you previously provided to us, in a portable and readily usable format to the extent that it is technically feasible to do so.
* Right to Opt Out. You may opt out of the processing of your personal data for the purposes of: i) targeted advertising, ii) the sale of personal data, or iii) profiling that may have a legal or other significant impact.

To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request [here](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3). You may also contact us by calling 1-833-796-0136 and entering 141439 as the PIN, or you may also contact us by email at copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com. We will use the information you provide to us solely for the purpose of verifying your request and locating your data, if any, within our records.

#### Non-discrimination

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for exercising any of your rights.

#### Authorized Agent

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request via an authorized agent acting on your behalf. To do so, we must receive written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.

### Important Information for Connecticut Residents: Your Connecticut Privacy Rights

These additional disclosures for Connecticut residents apply only to individuals who reside in Connecticut. The Connecticut Data Privacy Act provides additional rights to confirm and access, correct, delete, obtain a copy, and opt-out, and requires businesses collecting or disclosing personal information to provide notices and means to exercise those rights. The words used in this section have the meanings given to them in the CTDPA, which may be broader than their common meaning.

#### Notice of Collection

The categories of personal information that we may have collected in the past 12 months are:

Identifiers: name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol (IP) address, email address, account name. We may use this data to provide customers with an account which enables them to post listings or messages, or to subscribe to our newsletters. Additionally, we use online identifiers to understand how consumers use our products and services.

Customer records information: name, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit, or debit card number. We collect this information when a user performs a payment transaction on one of our services.

Commercial information: We use a unique identifier to track consumer behavior on our products. We then use that data to personalize content and/or advertising products to the consumer.

Internet or other electronic network activity information: We collect this data specific to our websites and applications. We do not operate a web browser or search technology, but we may track searches performed on our website. We do this for a few purposes. We allow users to create saved searches and alerts. Saved searches and alerts enable users to opt-in to a notification service. When the user creates a saved search, if a new product is posted on our service that matches their search criteria, we will send them an email or mobile phone alert. We also use their search behavior to personalize content and advertising.

Geolocation data: When using our service, a user can search for information using location data such as a city or zip code. Furthermore, on a mobile device, users can opt-in to the mobile device geolocation service to show the user listings from a selected mile radius from their current geolocation.

Inferences: We use consumer behavior to create profiles and make inferences about future consumer behavior.

We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes and sharing practices described in our policy above.

We do not generally “sell” personal information as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. However, to the extent “sale” under the CTDPA is interpreted to include advertising technology activities such as those disclosed in the above sections as a “sale,” we provide you the option to request that we not “sell” your personal information. We do not sell the personal information of minors known to be under the age of 16 without affirmative authorization.

We may sell or disclose the following categories of personal information for commercial purposes: identifiers, demographic information, commercial information, internet activity, geolocation data and inferences. We use and partner with different types of entities to assist with our daily operations and manage our services.

**What Are My Rights Under the CTDPA?** If you are a Connecticut resident and are engaged in a direct business relationship with Company as a consumer for the provision of the Sites or Services, you may have the following rights:

* Right to Confirm and to Access. You may confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data. You may also request access to your personal data.

Though you may request specific pieces of your personal information that we have collected, we may not provide the following information in order to protect the security of such information: social security numbers, driver’s license or other state or government-issued identification numbers, bank account numbers or other financial information, any health insurance or medical identification numbers or related information, account passwords or security questions and answers.

* Right to Correct. You may request the correction of any inaccuracies in your personal data, taking into account the nature of the personal data and the purposes of the processing of the personal data.
* Right to Delete. Under certain, limited circumstances, you may request that we delete personal information that we have collected from you or from a third party. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity, we will review your request to see if an exception allowing us to retain the information applies.
* Right to Obtain a Copy. You may request a copy of your personal data, which you previously provided to us, in a portable and readily usable format to the extent that it is technically feasible to do so.
* Right to Opt Out. You may opt out of the processing of your personal data for the purposes of: i) targeted advertising, ii) the sale of personal data, or iii) profiling that may have a legal or other significant impact.

To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request [here](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3). You may also contact us by calling 1-833-796-0136 and entering 141439 as the PIN, or you may also contact us by email at copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com. We will use the information you provide to us solely for the purpose of verifying your request and locating your data, if any, within our records.

#### Non-discrimination

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for exercising any of your rights.

#### Authorized Agent

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request via an authorized agent acting on your behalf. To do so, we must receive written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.

### Important Information for Nevada Residents: Your Nevada Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of Nevada, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of certain Personal Data to third parties who intend to license or sell that Personal Data. You can exercise this right by contacting us [here](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3).

### Important Information for Utah Residents: Your Utah Privacy Rights

These additional disclosures for Utah residents apply only to individuals who reside in Utah. The Utah Consumer Privacy Act provides additional rights to confirm, access, delete, obtain a copy, and opt-out, and requires businesses collecting or disclosing personal information to provide notices and means to exercise those rights. The words used in this section have the meanings given to them in the UCPA, which may be broader than their common meaning.

#### Notice of Collection

The categories of personal information that we may have collected in the past 12 months are:

Identifiers: name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol (IP) address, email address, account name. We may use this data to provide customers with an account which enables them to post listings or messages, or to subscribe to our newsletters. Additionally, we use online identifiers to understand how consumers use our products and services.

Customer records information: name, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit, or debit card number. We collect this information when a user performs a payment transaction on one of our services.

Commercial information: We use a unique identifier to track consumer behavior on our products. We then use that data to personalize content and/or advertising products to the consumer.

Internet or other electronic network activity information: We collect this data specific to our websites and applications. We do not operate a web browser or search technology, but we may track searches performed on our website. We do this for a few purposes. We allow users to create saved searches and alerts. Saved searches and alerts enable users to opt-in to a notification service. When the user creates a saved search, if a new product is posted on our service that matches their search criteria, we will send them an email or mobile phone alert. We also use their search behavior to personalize content and advertising.

Geolocation data: When using our service, a user can search for information using location data such as a city or zip code. Furthermore, on a mobile device, users can opt-in to the mobile device geolocation service to show the user listings from a selected mile radius from their current geolocation.

Inferences: We use consumer behavior to create profiles and make inferences about future consumer behavior.

We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes and sharing practices described in our policy above.

We do not generally “sell” personal information as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. However, to the extent “sale” under the UCPA is interpreted to include advertising technology activities such as those disclosed in the above sections as a “sale,” we provide you the option to request that we not “sell” your personal information. We do not sell the personal information of minors known to be under the age of 13 without affirmative authorization.

We may sell or disclose the following categories of personal information for commercial purposes: identifiers, demographic information, commercial information, internet activity, geolocation data and inferences. We use and partner with different types of entities to assist with our daily operations and manage our services.

**What Are My Rights Under the UCPA?** If you are a Utah resident and are engaged in a direct business relationship with Company as a consumer for the provision of the Sites or Services, you may have the following rights:

* Right to Confirm and to Access. You may confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data. You may also request access to your personal data.

Though you may request specific pieces of your personal information that we have collected, we may not provide the following information in order to protect the security of such information: social security numbers, driver’s license or other state or government-issued identification numbers, bank account numbers or other financial information, any health insurance or medical identification numbers or related information, account passwords or security questions and answers.

* Right to Delete. Under certain circumstances, you may request that we delete personal information that we have collected from you or from a third party. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity, we will review your request to see if an exception allowing us to retain the information applies.
* Right to Obtain a Copy. You may request a copy of your personal data, which you previously provided to us, in a portable and readily usable format to the extent that it is technically feasible to do so.
* Right to Opt Out. You may opt out of the processing of your personal data for the purposes of: i) targeted advertising, or ii) the sale of personal data.

To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request [here](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3). You may also contact us by calling 1-833-796-0136 and entering 141439 as the PIN, or you may also contact us by email at copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com. We will use the information you provide to us solely for the purpose of verifying your request and locating your data, if any, within our records.

#### Non-discrimination

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for exercising any of your rights.

#### Authorized Agent

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request via an authorized agent acting on your behalf. To do so, we must receive written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.

### Important Information for Virginia Residents: Your Virginia Privacy Rights

These additional disclosures for Virginia residents apply only to individuals who reside in Virginia. The Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act provides additional rights to confirm and access, correct, delete, obtain a copy, and opt out, and requires businesses collecting or disclosing personal information to provide notices and means to exercise those rights. The words used in this section have the meanings given to them in the CDPA, which may be broader than their common meaning.

#### Notice of Collection

The categories of personal information that we may have collected in the past 12 months are:

Identifiers: name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol (IP) address, email address, account name. We may use this data to provide customers with an account which enables them to post listings or messages, or to subscribe to our newsletters. Additionally, we use online identifiers to understand how consumers use our products and services.

Customer records information: name, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit, or debit card number. We collect this information when a user performs a payment transaction on one of our services.

Commercial information: We use a unique identifier to track consumer behavior on our products. We then use that data to personalize content and/or advertising products to the consumer.

Internet or other electronic network activity information: We collect this data specific to our websites and applications. We do not operate a web browser or search technology, but we may track searches performed on our website. We do this for a few purposes. We allow users to create saved searches and alerts. Saved searches and alerts enable users to opt-in to a notification service. When the user creates a saved search, if a new product is posted on our service that matches their search criteria, we will send them an email or mobile phone alert. We also use their search behavior to personalize content and advertising.

Geolocation data: When using our service, a user can search for information using location data such as a city or zip code. Furthermore, on a mobile device, users can opt-in to the mobile device geolocation service to show the user listings from a selected mile radius from their current geolocation.

Inferences: We use consumer behavior to create profiles and make inferences about future consumer behavior.

We collect and use these categories of personal information for the business purposes and sharing practices described in our policy above.

We do not generally “sell” personal information as the term “sell” is traditionally understood. However, to the extent “sale” under the CDPA is interpreted to include advertising technology activities such as those disclosed in the above sections as a “sale,” we provide you the option to request that we not “sell” your personal information. We do not sell the personal information of minors known to be under the age of 16 without affirmative authorization.

We may sell or disclose the following categories of personal information for commercial purposes: identifiers, demographic information, commercial information, internet activity, geolocation data and inferences. We use and partner with different types of entities to assist with our daily operations and manage our services.

**What Are My Virginia Personal Data Rights?** If you are a Virginia resident and are engaged in a direct business relationship with Company as a consumer for provision of the Sites or Services, you may have the following rights:

* Right to Confirm and to Access. You may confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data. You may also request access to your personal data.

Though you may request specific pieces of your personal information that we have collected, we may not provide the following information in order to protect the security of such information: social security numbers, driver’s license or other state or government issued identification numbers, bank account numbers or other financial information, any health insurance or medical identification numbers or related information, account passwords or security questions and answers.

* Right to Correct. You may request the correction of any inaccuracies in your personal data, taking into account the nature of the personal data and the purposes of the processing of the personal data.
* Right to Delete. Under certain, limited circumstances, you may request that we delete personal information that we have collected from you or maintain about you. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity, we will review your request to see if an exception allowing us to retain the information applies.
* Right to Obtain a Copy. You may request a copy of your personal data, which you previously provided to us, in a portable and readily usable format to the extent that it is technically feasible to do so.
* Right to Opt Out. You may opt out of the processing of your personal data for the purposes of: i) targeted advertising, ii) the sale of personal data, or iii) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request [here](https://privacyportal.cookiepro.com/webform/8becd7f7-c923-4cd4-814a-e08c34baf60b/f5166605-38e6-4c90-b937-5fc0da2d55a3). You may also contact us by calling 1-833-796-0136 and entering 141439 as the PIN, or you may also contact us by email at copyrightagent@bnmediallc.com. We will use the information you provide to us solely for the purpose of verifying your request and locating your data, if any, within our records.

#### Non-discrimination

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for exercising any of your rights.

#### Authorized Agent

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request via an authorized agent acting on your behalf. To do so, we must receive written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.

XIV. Users Outside the United States
------------------------------------

The Products are hosted in the United States and are governed by U.S. law. If you are using the Products from outside the United States, please be aware that any PII you share with us will be stored and processed in the United States where we locate and operate our servers and databases. By using the Products, you consent to the storage and processing of your PII at our facilities and the facilities of those third parties with whom we share your PII as described in this Policy.
